{
    "questions": [

        {
            "flashCardFront": "<img src='https://media.kanjialive.com/radical_character/hi.svg'/>",
            "flashCardBack": "ニチ、ジツ",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Meaning",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "ニチ、ジツ", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "ゲツ、ガツ", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "ボク、モク", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "<img src='https://media.kanjialive.com/radical_character/tsuki.svg' />",
            "flashCardBack": "ゲツ、ガツ",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Meaning",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "ゲツ、ガツ", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "ニチ、ジツ", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "ボク、モク", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "<img src='https://media.kanjialive.com/radical_character/ki.svg' />",
            "flashCardBack": "ボク、モク",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Meaning",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "ボク、モク", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "ニチ、ジツ", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "ゲツ、ガツ", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "<img src='https://media.kanjialive.com/radical_character/yama.svg'/>",
            "flashCardBack": "サン",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Meaning",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "サン", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "セン", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "デン", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "<img src='https://media.kanjialive.com/radical_character/sanbongawa.svg' />",
            "flashCardBack": "セン",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Meaning",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "セン", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "サン", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "デン", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "<img src='https://media.kanjialive.com/radical_character/ta.svg' />",
            "flashCardBack": "デン",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Meaning",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "デン", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "サン", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "セン", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "<img src='https://media.kanjialive.com/radical_character/hito.svg'/>",
            "flashCardBack": "ジン、ニン",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Meaning",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "ジン、ニン", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "コウ、ク", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "シャ", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "<img src='https://media.kanjialive.com/radical_character/kuchi.svg' />",
            "flashCardBack": "コウ、ク",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Meaning",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "コウ、ク", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "ジン、ニン", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "シャ", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "<img src='https://media.kanjialive.com/radical_character/kuruma.svg' />",
            "flashCardBack": "シャ",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Meaning",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "シャ", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "ジン、ニン", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "コウ、ク", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        },
        {
            "flashCardFront": "<img src='https://media.kanjialive.com/radical_character/mongamae.svg' />",
            "flashCardBack": "モン",
            "flashCardFlipped": false,
            "questionText": "Meaning",
            "answers": [
                {"answer": "モン", "correct": true, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "ジン、ニン", "correct": false, "selected": false},
                {"answer": "コウ、ク", "correct": false, "selected": false}
            ]
        }

    ]
}
